Hello
[music]
Hello friends welcome to Stroke Char today the
company we have chosen for you ICICI
Lombard Inc is a private company,
your company's IPO came in 2017 and
it was subscribed but then its
list in keyboard was doubled on a latest note
but if you see that the
lifting iron
of the company
and Kunigal if you are on the
channel has
increased by one and a half times in four years
and the stocks have been there for almost a year
and are 31.5 percent below the life height of your own friends,
subscribe now and buying stocks at level can
prove to be better,
subscribe to level as you know
company, along with the information of the company,
focus on the news related to the company and tractor company and
subscribe to the
video so that you can get complete information, so let's
start friends, Raghu had received the certificate of starting its operation in 2001 by India's second
largest private bank and
subscribe
company, at that
time the name of ICICI Bank was loan limit
cross, seven to four percent youth in the company was with
some other
company  Within two to three years of its operations, the
company became the largest private sector
general insurance company.
By 2005, the company had crossed the 1 million
mark.
In 2018, the company was the
largest private sector non-life insurance company in India based on gross direct premium income. The
company offers a wide and well-rounded range of products including motor insurance, health insurance, personal accident insurance,
crop insurance, etc. through multiple distribution channels. The
company's major distribution channels include direct
sales to individual
participants
and online,
through which the company services its customers.
In 2017, the
company became the first pure
general insurance company to be listed on this channel. The company had partnered with one of India
's leading and world's largest designated
insurance companies,
under which a comprehensive
internship program was launched for its customers
and a key
recruitment program was initiated by the
company. In 2018, the
company
became the first Indian company to be certified by the Insurance Regulatory and Development Authority of India Limited.  In
2021, it acquired Bharti AXA General
Insurance Company,
due to which more than one lakh people
joined the company through it and
today the number of customers in the company is more than four crore. The
company has till now reached approximately
1.5 crore. The company has more than 1500 branches in India
and
more than 300 hospitals in the network of companies.
If you look at the final
market cap of the company worth Rs. 1000 crore, then the
shareholder of 18% in the company is
22% and
6% in some other
subscriber. If
you look at the
shareholding in the company, the
government had appointed the first chief in 2015 for
insurance companies
and in an insurance company it is
approximately 5550%. It has been increased to
around 124%,
due to which the promoters will have to do less so that
foreign investment can increase in these companies.
And if you look at the sales cases of the last five years of the company, then after listing the company has
continuously increased, if you look at the company's sales, then
year after year the company  That
growth has continued and you can see that there has been
no impact on the company's sales in the mixed period
and secondly, if you look at it, the
banks have some percentage stake in the company in the last three quarters and you
can see that it is increasing
and also if you look at the nutrition, then at the
highest level, if you compare the nutrition report of the company
with other companies, it is the fourth largest company in the
market but if you look at the profit of the company, then in
terms of profit,
you can see
that
in terms of profit, the company has been at the first
position and
in terms of subscription, the company has been at the top level
and if you look at the valuation, the
company is at the cheapest valuation,
now as you can see,
at 55.47, the company's
valuation is
good
and also the debt of the company is equity
company
so insurance companies cannot be debt, let us
quickly
focus on some news related to the company
that in 2000, an Indian company was
acquired.  The
company had more than one lakh
companies and the
second
highest increase in the company was the
new FD of this company which was increased to
740. Today you will see that
from the side you can
see that the company recently established itself on
24 December
2001. The company offers dental medical insurance and has
a big network tie-up
with it.
Today's
latest news is that
for the change in the option of
third party motor insurance, the government has sought their opinion from these companies
till 26th January but
they agreed.
This will prove to be very good for the company in the coming times. If you
use Android to chart the stock price, you will see that the stock
monitor was burning in a fast train
and for some time now, in the last one year, if you
look at the chart on the daily chart of the company, you will
see that the stock has been
up from
1650 towards
12600. So you
can appoint this and those who have a
long term investment view in the market, click on the
subscribe button.  If you want to
subscribe to buy on the subscribe button, you should
carry it in your portfolio for the long term, so the
best company for tractors is the
vote level which is coming out from the stroke
of 1250, so as long as the stock spread is above the level,
carry the toss,
include it in your portfolio as per long term investment, in this way
you should do insurance companies,
you must have felt the need for them at the time of this submarine
and as you would know in India
that friends,
you can think of subscribing to the company in 12-15 days, friends
subscribe, the
company has been a strong company, the profit
of the company has been strong as per its tractor
related companies, so
you should definitely keep it on your Twitter, so that's all for
today's episode friends,
see you in the next video, if you
like the video then definitely subscribe to our channel,
share it, comment,
like it and if you want us to
bring a video on any company by you, then you
can tell in the comment section, so
in the next video till then, hello friends